Richard York Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artists' Artwork Files, circa 1865-2004, Series 2:; (Boxes 7-64; 56.85 linear feet)
  - General, circa 1865-2004, 2.1:
    - Schamberg, Morton Livingston, 4535CY: Composition, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Scharf, William, 8947CY: Wind Oval, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Scharf, William, 8948CY: Flesh Jail, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Scharf, William, 8949CY: An Asgardian Again [An Asgardian Angel?], 2002, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Scharf, William, 8950CY: Lassitude of the Acrobat, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Scharf, William, 8951CY: Ladder of Qualms and Fragrance, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Scharf, William, 9424CY: Trochee of Citrus, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Scharf, William, 9425CY: Again, the Pale Rope, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Scharf, William, 9426CY: A Mischief of Magnets, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Scharf, William, 9427CY: Sun Instrument, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Scharf, William, 9428CY: Bride of the Egg Bridge, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Scharf, William, 9429CY: The Grape Mask Quivers, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Scharf, William, 9430CY: Egg Echo, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - Scharf, William, 9431CY: Eagle Solitaire, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - Scharf, William, 9432CY: Argo Gone, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - Scharf, William, 9433CY: The Golden Bridle, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - Scharf, William, 9434CY: The White Rope, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - Scharf, William, 9435CY: Rescue by Envy, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 53)
    - Scharf, William, 9436CY: Birth of a Dark Bouquet, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 54)
    - Scharf, William, 9437CY: "But It Does Move," Said Galileo, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 55)
    - Scharf, William, 9438CY: Decant the Dawn, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 56)
    - Scharf, William, 9439CY: The Bruised Stitches, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 57)
    - Scharf, William, 9440CY: Icarus and the Wheat Angels, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 58)
    - Scharf, William, 9441CY: The Myth Mirror, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 59)
    - Scharf, William, 9442CY: By the Colors She Kept, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 60)
    - Scharf, William, 9443CY: A Shouldn't of Gold, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 61)
    - Scharf, William, 9444CY: Light By the White Candle, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 62)
    - Scharf, William, 9445CY: Honey and Cosmetic Snow, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 63)
    - Scharf, William, 9446CY: Chalaza Rite, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 64)
    - Scharf, William, 9447CY: The Martyr's Ladder, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 65)
    - Scharf, William, 9448CY: As Measure Praises Gold, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 66)
    - Scharf, William, 9449CY: At the Forgiving, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 67)
    - Scharf, William, 9460CY: Deify the Dawn, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 68)
    - Scharf, William, 9461CY: Light Blue Angel, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 69)
    - Scharf, William, 9462CY: Sun Mane, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 70)
    - Scharf, William, 9463CY: A Codicil for the History of Darkness, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 71)
    - Schell, F. Cresson, 246CY: Michigan Avenue, Chicago, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 72)
    - Schmauss, Peter, 1729CY: Park Slope, Brooklyn, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 73)
    - Schmidt, Katherine, 1469CY: The Men Clean Up, 1981-1985 (Box 49, Folder 74)
    - Schmitt, Carl, 7725JY: A Backyard in Brooklyn, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 75)
    - Schofield, Walter Elmer, 208CY: Village on the Seine, 1983-1984 (Box 49, Folder 76)
    - Schofield, Walter Elmer, 798CY: A Brook in Winter, 1982-1983 (Box 49, Folder 77)
    - Schofield, Walter Elmer, 1958CY: Schofield's Cottage, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 78)
    - Schofield, Walter Elmer, 2017RY: The Beech Wood, 1987-1990 (Box 49, Folder 79)
    - Schofield, Walter Elmer, 4139JY: White Sand Harbour, 1994, 2000-2001 (Box 49, Folder 80)
    - Schryver, Louis Marie de, 3462CY: Basket of Plums, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 81)
    - Schumacher, William Emil, 1167CY: Festival Night, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 82)
    - Schumacher, William Emil, 1172CY: Mother and Children, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 83)
    - Schumacher, William Emil, 1173CY: Chanson des Soldats Francaises, 1984-1985 (Box 49, Folder 84)
    - Schumacher, William Emil, 1174CY: The Ascension of the Virgin, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 85)
    - Schussele, Christian, 3914CY: At the Well, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 86)
    - Seager, Edward, 1417CY: Trestle Work, Cheat River, Virginia, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 87)
    - Seager, Edward, 1418CY: Monongahela Iron Bridge, Virginia, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 88)
    - Seager, Edward, 1583CY: Lake George, 1848, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 89)
    - Seager, Edward, 1584CY: Black Mountain, Lake George, 1848, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 90)
    - Sears, Philip, 8786JY: Stepping Stones, 2002-2004 (Box 49, Folder 91)
    - Sears, Sarah Choate, 6914CY: Poppies, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 92)
    - Seavey, G.W., 2353CY: Daffodils and Violets, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 93)
    - Seyfert, Leopold, 3498CY: Flower Arrangement, 1991-1993 (Box 49, Folder 94)
    - Seyfert, Leopold, 3499CY: Still Life: Poinsettias, 1991-1993 (Box 49, Folder 95)
    - Shahn, Ben, 1423CY: Boy Writing, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 96)
    - Shahn, Ben, 6102CY: Rena and Tom Mooney, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 97)
    - Sharp, Joseph Henry, 3562CY: Shelling Corn, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 98)
    - Shattuck, Aaron Draper, 147CY: Storm Over the Adirondacks, 1981-1984 (Box 49, Folder 99)
    - Shattuck, Aaron Draper, 979CY: Pansies in a Vase, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 100)
    - Shattuck, Aaron Draper, 1040CY: Sunset, 1983-1984 (Box 49, Folder 101)
    - Shattuck, Aaron Draper, 6569RY: Guernsey Cow, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 102)
    - Shattuck, Aaron Draper, 6843CY: Mount Washington and Pink Sunset, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 103)
    - Shattuck, Aaron Draper, 7140CY: Androscoggin River, New Hampshire, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 104)
    - Shaw, Charles, 299RY: Abstraction Number Four, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 105)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1843JY: Abstract Shapes, 1986, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 106)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1917CY: Intersecting Trapezoids, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 107)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1918CY: Textured Composition, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 108)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1919CY: Seated Nude, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 109)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1920CY: Textured Polygon, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 110)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1921CY: Composition in Green and Orange, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 111)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1922CY: Twilight, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 112)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1923CY: Manhattan Pattern, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 113)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1924CY: Abstract Forms IV, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 114)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1925CY: Abstraction, circa 1987 (Box 49, Folder 115)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1926CY: Abstract Forms II, 1987-1993 (Box 49, Folder 116)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1927CY: Pointillist Composition, 1987, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1928CY: Abstracted Still Life, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1929CY: Trapezoids, 1987-1989 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1930CY: The Dance, 1987-1993 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1931CY: Abstract Forms I, 1987-1993 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1932CY: Abstract Forms III, 1987-1993 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1933CY: East River, 1987, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1934CY: Composition in Green, Brown, and Orange, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1935CY: Manhattan Motif, 1987-1993 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1936CY: Mannequin, 1987-1993 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1971CY: Fifth Avenue, 1987, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Shaw, Charles, 1979CY: Abstraction #4, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Shaw, Charles, 3451CY: Plastic Polygon, 1991, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Shaw, Charles, 4604CY: Twilight, 1987-1998 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Shaw, Charles, 6111CY: Abstraction, 1987, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Shaw, Charles, 6247CY: Composition 17, 1998-1999 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Shaw, Charles, 6910CY: Homage to Klee, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Shaw, Charles, 6922CY: Polygon Relief, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Shaw, Charles Green, 8945CY: Kite Abstraction, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Shaw, Joshua, 142CY: Sunrise, 1981-1984 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Shaw, Joshua, 2656CY: View in Western Pennsylvania, 1983-1990 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Sheard, Thomas Frederick Mason, 366CY: Boy With Sling Shot, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Sheeler, Charles 231CY: Barn, 1981-1987 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 497CY: Rose, 1982-1984 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 734JY: Red Tulips, 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 735JY: White Tulips, circa 2002 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 806CY: Landscape #1: Abstraction Tree Form, circa 1982 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 820CY: Farm Buildings in Landscape, 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Sheeler, Charles 829CY: Dahlias, circa 1982 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 1419CY: Convergence II, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 2155CY: Summer Flowers, 1987-1995 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 2721JY: Two Against White, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 3267CY: Canyons II, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 3301CY: Electric Power, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 3527CY: Rose, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    - Sheeler, Charles (Attributed), 3561LY: White House, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 3683CY: Apple Tree, circa 1920, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 3684CY: Calla Lily, 1992-1998 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 3685CY: Lhasa, 1992, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 3871CY: The Great Tree, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 4095CY: Hallway (Interior), 1988-1999 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 4111CY: Farm Buildings in Landscape, 1982-1983, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 4608CY: San Francisco - Fisherman's Wharf, 1987-1988, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 43)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 4756CY: Tree Trunk #2, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 44)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 4959CY: California Industrial, 1996-2000 (Box 50, Folder 45)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 6992RY: Study: New York #3, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 46)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 8000CY: Meta-Mold, 2001-2003 (Box 50, Folder 47)
    - Sheeler, Charles, 8926CY: White Tulips, 1982-1983, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 48)
    - Shepler, I.D., 4735RY: Texas Bluebonnets, 1995-1997, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 49)
    - Sheppard, William Ludlow, 3354CY: Firing the Flintlock, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 50)
    - Shields, Phyllis, 813LY: Still Life with Iris, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 51)
    - Shields, Phyllis, 814LY: Floral Still Life, circa 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 52)
    - Shields, Phyllis, 1018RY: Farewell, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 53)
    - Shields, Phyllis, 6060JY: Schoolroom, 1997, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 54)
    - Shinn, Everett, 245RY: Portrait of Mrs. Stewart, 1981-1983 (Box 50, Folder 55)
    - Shinn, Everett, 369JY: The Cabbie, 1961, 1981-1985 (Box 50, Folder 56)
    - Shinn, Everett, 1392CY: Dancer With Fan, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 57)
    - Shinn, Everett, 1393CY: Irving Place Burlesque, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 58)
    - Shinn, Everett, 1442CY: Falling Leaves, 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 59)
    - Shinn, Everett, 1449CY: Woman Undressing, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 60)
    - Shinn, Everett, 1706CY: Outdoor Stage, Paris or Girl With Black Gloves, 1984, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 61)
    - Shinn, Everett, 1883CY: Street Scene, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 62)
    - Shinn, Everett, 2629CY: Woman Undressing, 1989, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 63)
    - Shinn, Everett, 2922CY: Washington Arch, After the Rain, 1990-1995 (Box 50, Folder 64)
    - Shinn, Everett, 3039CY: St. Patrick's, 1990-1994 (Box 50, Folder 65)
    - Shinn, Everett, 3158CY: Flapper, 1990-1991 (Box 50, Folder 66)
    - Shinn, Everett, 4719CY: Performer, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 67)
    - Shinn, Everett, 4873CY: Fair-Man in Rain, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 68)
    - Shinn, Everett, 5055CY: Street Vendor, Paris, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 69)
    - Shinn, Everett, 6874CY: Battle of the Clowns, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 70)
    - Shinn, Everett, 6902CY: Fire on Mott Street, 1999-2000 (Box 50, Folder 71)
    - Shinn, Everett, 7609LY: Fire on Mott Street, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 72)
    - Shirlaw, Walter, 181CY: Little Street Musicians, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 73)
    - Shirlaw, Walter, 2274RY: Abundance of Land and Sea, 1988-1996 (Box 50, Folder 74)
    - Shore, Henrietta, 3960CY: Gladiola, 1993-1994 (Box 50, Folder 75)
    - Shore, Henrietta, 4990CY: Cypress Trees, Point Lobos, 1996-1997 (Box 50, Folder 76)
    - Shore, Henrietta, 5080CY: California Data, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 77)
    - Shore, Henrietta, 5081CY: Point Sur Lighthouse, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 78)
    - Shulman, Morris, 4494CY: Adult Education Class, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 79)
    - Shuttleworth, Claire, 2122JY: Hollyhocks, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 80)
    - Shuttleworth, Claire, 2165RY: Rapids Above the Falls, 1987-1993, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 81)
    - Silva, Francis A., 1054CY: Moonrise on the New England Coast, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 82)
    - Silva, Francis A., 1105CY: Moonrise over New York Harbor, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 83)
    - Silva, Francis A., 1826CY: Hudson from the Tappanzee, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 84)
    - Silva, Francis A., 2210CY: The Coastal Scene, 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 85)
    - Silva, Francis A., 3113CY: The Coastal Scene, 1990, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 86)
    - Silva, Francis A., 3396LY: Moonrise over New York Harbor, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 87)
    - Silva, Francis A., 3432CY: Moonrise on the New England Coast, 1991, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 88)
    - Silva, Francis A., 3919CY: Moonrise over New York Harbor, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 89)
    - Silva, Francis A., 3949RY: Gloucester Dawn, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 90)
    - Silva, Francis A., 3970CY: Great South Bay off Fire Island, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 91)
    - Silva, Francis A., 4479CY: Venetian Boats, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 92)
    - Silva, Francis A., 7452RY: North River, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 93)
    - Simmons, Edward E., 2861CY: Portrait, 1989-1993 (Box 50, Folder 94)
    - Simmons, Edward E., 4384RY: Mother and Child, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 95)
    - Simmons, Edward E., 4942CY, 4943CY: The Bosom of the Land (Pair), 1996 (Box 50, Folder 96)
    - Simmons, Edward E., 5097RY: Landscape, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 97)
    - Simmons, Edward E., 6625CY: Afternoon Wind, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 98)
    - Simmons, Edward E., 7113CY: Our Backyard, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 99)
    - The Simpson Theater Collection, 2901CY: Scenic Designs for the American Musical Theater on Broadway, 1989-1990 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Singzenich, Eugene, 1688CY: The Milwaukee, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Slayton, Miss Franc, 4403CY: The Destruction of Jerusalem, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Sloan, John, 295RY: Corral in the Canyon, 1981-1983 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Sloan, John, 368RY: Burros Threshing, 1981-1983 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Sloan, John, 673CY: Evening, Arroyo, 1982-1985 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Sloan, John, 1443CY: Wellington Held Forth a Wedge of Layer Cake, 1983-1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Sloan, John, 1445CY: Boy with Piccolo, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Sloan, John, 2631CY: Wellington Held Forth a Wedge of Layer Cake, 1989, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Sloan, John, 3904CY: Schuylkill River, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Sloan, John, 4725CY: He Lost Himself in the Rehearsal, 1995-1997 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Sloan, John, 6528RY: Nude Sketches, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Sloan, John, 7034CY: Spring Creek, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Sloan, John, 7035CY: Autumn on the River, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Smart, Mrs. J.E., 2196RY: Bowl of Strawberries, 1987, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Smedley, William Thomas, 2477CY: The Conversation, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Smibert, John (Attributed), 4637LY: Portrait of a Woman, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Smillie, George: Keene Valley, New York, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Smillie, George, 192CY: Mill Pond at Ridgefield, Connecticut, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Smillie, George, 4254CY: Adirondack Mountains, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Smillie, James D., 1573CY: Sabbath Day Point, Lake George, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Smillie, James D., 4255CY: In the Wilderness, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Smillie, James D., 7036CY: Among the Hills in October, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Smith, David, 4400CY: Menand VI, 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Smith, F. Carl, 6990CY: Luxemborg Garden, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Francis Hopkinson, 785CY: Garden at the Manor House, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Francis Hopkinson, 801CY: The Visit, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Smith, Francis Hopkinson, 836CY: The Voorstraat Haven, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Smith, Francis Hopkinson, 1618CY: At the Port of Havana, Cuba, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Smith, Henry Knox, 931CY: Distant Heights, 1981-1985 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Smith, Henry Knox, 932CY: Crops Up Somewhere, 1983, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Smith, Henry Knox, 933CY: Opalescence, 1983, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Smith, Henry Knox, 934CY: Curious Dreams, 1983, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Smith, Henry Knox, 935CY: Vitality Flows, 1983, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Smith, [Henry] Knox, 3363CY: Repressed Mathematics, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Henry Pember, 105CY: Landscape with Lake, 1981-1985 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Smith, Henry Pember, 1353CY: Home, Sweet Home, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Smith, Henry Pember, 2623RY: Summer Landscape, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Smith, Henry Pember, 3130CY: The Old Homestead, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 4891CY, 7626CY-7638CY [Smith Trust], 1996, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 6637CY: Harbor: Antafagasta, Chile, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 6638CY: Sunlit Cliff, Massachusetts, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 6640CY: End of Pawley's Island, South Carolina, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 6641CY: A Boardwalk on Pawley's, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 6642CY: Comet, New Mexico, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 6682CY: Red Tiled House, circa 1998 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 7032CY: Provincetown, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 7130CY: View From the Dunes, circa 2001 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 7631CY: Poison Ivy/Cape Cod, 2000-2001 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 7650CY: Cityscape, 2001, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 7731CY: Double House, circa 2001 (Box 51, Folder 51)
    - Smith, Houghton Cranford, 7732CY: The Accommodation, circa 2001 (Box 51, Folder 52)
    - Smith, Mary Priscilla, 8970CY: Botanical, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Smith, Mary Priscilla, 8971CY: Botanical, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Smith, Mary Priscilla, 8972CY: Botanical, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 55)
    - Smith, Mary Priscilla, 8973CY: Botanical, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 56)
    - Smith, Russell, 8964CY: Jordan's Knob on Conecocheague Creek, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 57)
    - Smith, Walter Granville, 273CY: Portrait of a Lady, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 58)
    - Smith, Xanthus, 4343CY: Fort Delaware, 1987, 1994, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 59)
    - Smith, Xanthus, 4344CY: Fort Delaware at Head of Delaware Bay, 1990-1995 (Box 51, Folder 60)
    - Snead, Stella, 6846CY: The Green Witch, 1998, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 61)
    - Snyder, Annie M., 3500CY: Basket of Fruit, 1991-1997 (Box 51, Folder 62)
    - Sohon, Gustavus, 4610CY: Colonel Wright's Campaign, 8 Sketches, 1995-1997 (Box 51, Folder 63)
    - Sommer, William, 815CY: Iris, circa 1982 (Box 51, Folder 64)
    - Sommer, William, 1330CY: Brandywine Landscape with Barrel, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 65)
    - Sonntag, William Louis, 194CY: A Landscape with Lake, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 66)
    - Sonntag, William Louis, 802CY: Landscape, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 67)
    - Sonntag, William Louis, 982CY: Petunias, 1983-1985 (Box 51, Folder 68)
    - Sonntag, William Louis, 1198CY: Eastern Mountain Landscape, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 69)
    - Sonntag, William Louis, 1512CY: Sunset: A View in Chenango, New York, 1985-1987 (Box 51, Folder 70)
    - Sonntag, William Louis, Jr., 3575CY: Shipwreck, 1992 (Box 51, Folder 71)
    - Sonntag, William Louis, 6527CY: Late Summer, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 72)
    - Soyer, Isaac, 2613CY: Still-Life: Fruit, circa 1989 (Box 51, Folder 73)
    - Soyer, Moses, 7087CY: Nude, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 74)
    - Soyer, Raphael, 7086CY: Woman, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 75)
    - Speicher, Eugene, 995CY: Modern Venus, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 76)
    - Speicher, Eugene, 2186JY: Passing Storm, 1987-1988 (Box 51, Folder 77)
    - Spencer, John C., 4435CY: Roses in a Glass, 1995, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 78)
    - Spencer, Lilly Martin: Life Without Hope, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 79)
    - Spencer, Lilly Martin, 1788CY: Peeling Onions, 1986-1988 (Box 51, Folder 80)
    - Spencer, Lilly Martin, 2204CY: Dixie Land, 1987-1990 (Box 51, Folder 81)
    - Spencer, Lilly Martin (Attributed), 4457CY: Portrait of a Lady, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 82)
    - Spencer, Lilly Martin, 5099CY: Picnic on the Fourth of July, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 83)
    - Spencer, Lilly Martin, 6350CY: Blue Ribbon Cat, 1998, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 84)
    - Spencer, Niles, 3061CY: Study for Buildings, 1990-1994 (Box 51, Folder 85)
    - Spencer, Niles, 3895CY: Untitled (Gramophone), 1993 (Box 51, Folder 86)
    - Spencer, Niles, 3896CY: Untitiled (Cello), 1993 (Box 51, Folder 87)
    - Spencer, Niles, 4446CY: University Place, 1981, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 88)
    - Spencer, Niles, 4576CY: Building Theme, circa 1995 (Box 51, Folder 89)
    - Spencer, Robert, 195CY: Waterloo Row, 1982-1984 (Box 51, Folder 90)
    - Spencer, Robert, 1197CY: Court at Dusk, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 91)
    - Spencer, Robert, 2260CY: By the Seine, 1988, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 92)
    - Sprinchorn, Carl, 2757CY: Zinnias, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 93)
    - Sprinchorn, Carl, 7030CY: Glory of Fall, New Brunswick, Canada, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 94)
    - Stamos, Theodoros, 3375CY: Untitled, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 95)
    - Stanfield, William C. (Attributed), 4097CY: Sailing Boats in Estuary Off Dutch Coast, 1993-1996 (Box 51, Folder 96)
    - Stanley, John Mix, 1647CY: Mt. Hays Near Gorham, New Hampshire, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 97)
    - Stark, L., 3981CY: Watermelon, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 98)
    - Steichen, Edward, 1098CY: Landscape With Avenue of Trees, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 99)
    - Stella, Joseph, 241CY: Rhododendrons, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 100)
    - Stella, Joseph, 244JY: Nude Torso, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 101)
    - Stella, Joseph, 255JY: Sunflowers and Gourds, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 102)
    - Stella, Joseph, 292RY: Lotus, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 103)
    - Stella, Joseph, 307CY: Tropical Flowers/Azalea, 1981, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 104)
    - Stella, Joseph, 308RY: Pink Delphinium, 1981, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 105)
    - Stella, Joseph, 309CY: Cherry Branch With Two Roses, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 106)
    - Stella, Joseph, 310CY: Rhododendron Cluster, 1981, 1983 (Box 51, Folder 107)
    - Stella, Joseph, 311CY: Chick Weed, 1981-1983 (Box 51, Folder 108)
    - Stella, Joseph, 312CY: Rhododendron Cluster With Green Leaves, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 109)
    - Stella, Joseph, 313CY: Yellow Tropical Flower, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 110)
    - Stella, Joseph, 314CY: Flowers With Dogwood, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 111)
    - Stella, Joseph, 315CY: Succulent Plant With Orange Blossoms, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Stella, Joseph, 316RY: Blue and Purple Iris, 1981, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Stella, Joseph, 317CY: White Tuberose Begonia, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 3)